where2go.com 2016-11-24

# Where2Go.com - The Place to Find a Business on the Web

**Privacy Policy**

**This policy will tell you:**

  1. What personally identifiable information does Where2go.com collect from me?
  2. What are cookies and how does Where2go use them?
  3. How does Where2go use my information?
  4. Who is collecting the information?
  5. With whom does Where2go share my information?
  6. What are my choices regarding the collection, use, and distribution of my information?
  7. What is Where2go's policy on allowing me to update, correct, or delete my personally information?
  8. What security precautions are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of my information?
  9. What additional Information & privacy resources are on the web?

* * *

**What personally identifiable information does Where2go collect from me?**

Where2go collects information in several different situations. 

  1. Business Listings: 

Personal and business information is gathered if you register a business website with the Where2go search engine. This information is segmented into public and private information. 

Your public information such as business name, public contact info, address, products & services, years in business, etc are made available to all users of the Where2go search engine. 

Your private information (administrative contact information) is considered confidential and is only used by us to authenticate your access to your listing so you may modify or update it and for us to have a point of contact with the person responsible for your listing. 

Your administrative contact will receive a minimum of one annual email from Where2go requesting that you update your listing. This is done to keep the Where2go database current and reminds you to review your listing and update any data that may have changed. 

You may update your listing as often as you like by using the admin username and password you selected when you registered your site. At this time Where2go only lists business websites. 

  2. Contest Entries: 

We may ask you for personal information when you enter a sweepstakes, contest or promotion sponsored by either Where2go and/or any of our members. 

  3. Direct Contact: 

If you contact Where2go we may keep a record of that correspondence including any personal information you supply including your email address. 

  4. Surveys: 

Where2go occasionally asks users to complete surveys that we use for research purposes and to make our site better. If the survey is being done for a third party we will inform you prior to you submitting any data. 

Whenever Where2go collects personal information we make an effort to include an indication of the intended use of the information and a link to this policy statement. 

* * *

**What are cookies and how does Where2go use them?**

To make your searching experience better Where2go uses "cookies" to store and track information about your unique "user session". A cookie is a unique number that is sent to your browser from our web server and is temporarily stored on your computer. 

Generally, we use cookies to: 

  1. To track your "user session". This allows us to do such things as have our search engine remember what you just searched for and retain it on multiple pages. It is also used to allow "next 20" functionality on our search results lists. If we did not track your user session you would not be able to get the next 20 matches without running a new search. 
  2. To make entering contest easier and faster. When you enter a contest on Where2go you are given the opportunity of having Where2go remember you (by accepting a cookie) so that the next time you wish to enter a contest you do not need to fill out the entire entry form again - a real time saver! 
  3. To track your progress and number of entries in some promotions or contests. Just as cookies allow us to keep track of your searches, they are used to track your progress through entering a drawing, contest or promotion. 
  4. To monitor network traffic patterns. By knowing how people navigate through our site and what features they use most we can make Where2go.com better. 

Any advertising from others that may appear on Where2go may use their own cookies. 

Where2go also collects IP addresses for security, system administration and to assist us in generating aggregate usage information. 

Where2go uses sophisticated anti-hacking technology that, when enabled by a suspected hacking attempt, will collect as much network and client machine information as is available, including any unique hardware ids including your network card and motherboard serial numbers and the full path back to your computer. This information is only collected if your computer is suspected of an attempt to hack our network. If a hacking attempt is verified, this information will be turned over to the proper legal authorities for prosecution. 

* * *

**How does Where2go use my information?**

Where2go's primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you with a better web experience and better service. Where2go listed businesses are required to provide administrative contact information to allow them to securely access and update their listing. This information also allows us to keep them informed of new services and features here at Where2go.com. 

Users who register for a contest or promotion provide limited contact and demographic information that allows us to contact them about the status of the contest or promotion (i.e.: you've won or lost) and with their permission notify them of other contests and promotions that may be of interest to them. 

We do **not** use this information to send you unsolicited emails (or spam). 

Where2go does do research on our users' demographics, interests, and how they use our site, based on information provided to us upon registration, during a promotion, from our server logs or from our on-line surveys. We do this to make our site better. This research is compiled and analyzed on an aggregated basis (meaning we do not single out specific users). Where2go may publish or share this aggregated data. 

* * *

**Who is collecting the information?**

When you are on Where2go.com and are asked for any information, unless specifically stated otherwise, you are providing that information only to Where2go. As stated earlier all business listing administrative contact information is considered by us to be confidential and is not released to anyone outside Where2go. 

However, there are circumstances where information you provide must be shared with a third party - such as a contest offered by someone other than Where2go. For example, some Where2go services, like our contest section may have contests offered by others; it may be necessary for us to share the information you provide with the company offering the contest. If data is being collected, transferred or maintained by any company other than Where2go, you will be notified prior to submitting the data. If you do not want your data to be shared, you can choose not to enter that specific contest or promotion. 

Promotions that run on Where2go may be sponsored by companies other than Where2go or may be co-sponsored by Where2go and another company. Some or all data collected during a promotion may be shared with the sponsor. If data will be shared, you will be notified prior to submitting the data. If you don't want your data to be shared, all you need to do is not participate in the promotion. 

Please be aware that Where2go advertisers and listed web sites that have links on our site may collect personally identifiable information about you. The information practices of these advertisers, members and web sites are not covered by this privacy statement. 

* * *

**With whom does Where2go share my information?**

As a general rule, Where2go will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information except when we have your permission or under special circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that the law requires it or under the circumstances described below. The following describes some of the ways that your information may be disclosed. 

_Data in the Aggregate_ : Where2go discloses aggregated user statistics (for example, 68% of our users run Windows 98) in order to describe our services to current and prospective partners, advertisers, and other third parties, and for other lawful purposes such as providing internet usages and trend data to the media. This data is always as an aggregate and is never released for a single specific user. 

_Other:_ Where2go may also disclose account information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating Where2go's Usage Policy or may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) Where2go's rights or property, other Where2go users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. Where2go may disclose or access account information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it and for administrative and other purposes that we deem necessary to maintain, service, and improve our products and services. 

* * *

**What are my choices regarding the collection, use, and distribution of my information?**

Where2go may, from time to time, send you email regarding our products and services. Listed businesses agree to receive annual membership update requests via email. 

In addition, if you indicated upon registration that you are interested in receiving offers or other information from Where2go and our partners, we may occasionally send you email about products and services that we feel may be of interest to you. Only Where2go will send you these emails and only if you indicated that you want to receive such offers. If you do not want to receive such mailings, simply indicate this when signing up, or, at any time by editing your Where2go Account Information to no longer receive such mailings. 

On some types of Where2go promotions, we will ask for your email address in order to update you on your score, entries, and status. When you participate in these types of promotions, you may (depending on the promotion) receive promotion-related email, unless you choose the no-email option that some promotions offer. 

You also have choices with respect to cookies. By modifying your browser preferences, you have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies. If you choose to reject all cookies you may be unable to use those Where2go services that require cookies in order to operate. 

* * *

**What is Where2go's policy on allowing me to update, correct, or delete my personally information?**

If you have a Where2go business listing you may modify, update or delete your listing and your confidential administrative contact information at any time by visiting our member services page. You will need your user name and password to access your listing. 

Should you decide to delete your Where2go business listing it will no longer appear on our public site, however your original information may be retained within our database and on our backups. 

If you have elected to enable the "remember me" feature for contests on Where2go you can update or delete your information at any time by visiting the contest members page. 

* * *

**What security precautions are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of my information?**

Your Where2go business listing is password-protected so that you and only you have access to your confidential administrative contact information. You may edit your Where2go business listing by using your user name and password. 

If you have elected to activate the "remember me" feature of Where2go you will have selected a password that together with your email address will give you access to your information. 

We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. Where2go will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or email. If you forget your password there is a mechanism to have it emailed to you on each password entry screen. 

We have taken steps to ensure the security of our data - it is important that you practice safe computing and remember to sign out of your Where2go account and close your browser when you have finished your work. Never give your user name and password to anyone and avoid accessing your personal Where2go information from a computer you share with someone else or are using at a public place like a library or Internet cafe. 

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, Where2go cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or through us, and you do so at your own risk. 

* * *

**Additional Information**

If you have a question that was not addressed in this privacy policy you may contact us at [info@where2go.com](mailto:info@where2go.com) or at the following: 

Where2go   
PO 1589   
Oak View, CA 93022 

**Also see...**   
[Electronic Frontier Foundation](http://www.eff.org/) \- a civil liberties organization working to protect your rights online. 

[How to Protect Your Privacy](http://www.ftc.gov/privacy/index.html) \- information from the Federal Trade Commission for consumers. 

[Kids Privacy](http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/edcams/kidzprivacy/) \- information from the Federal Trade Commission about kids' privacy and the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act. 

* * *

Copyright © 2000 Where2go Inc. All rights reserved.
